<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tourist Guide</string>
    <string name="welcome_tourist_guide">Welcome To\n
    My Personal Chef</string>
    <string name="a_food_experience_in_telangana_is_also_something_to_look_forward_to_when_visiting_this_south_indian_state">A food Experience in Telangana is also something to look forward to when visiting this south indian state</string>
    <string name="button">Golconda Fort</string>
    <string name="charminar">Charminar</string>
    <string name="t2">CHARMINAR</string>
    <string name="t3">historic monument located at the heart of Hyderabad, west-central Telangana state, south-central India. The city, which is the capital of both Telangana and Andhra Pradesh states, was also the capital of the historic princely state of Hyderabad.
        The monument was built in 1591 by Muḥammad Qulī Quṭb Shah, the fifth king of the Quṭb Shāhī dynasty, reportedly as the first building in Hyderabad, his new capital. Over the years, it has become a signature monument to and an iconic symbol of the city’s heritage. According to one legend, the Hyderabad region was reeling from a devastating plague at the time that Muḥammad Qulī Quṭb Shah was shifting his capital from nearby Golconda to the new city. He commemorated the end of the plague by building a mosque, which became known as Charminar because of its four towering and distinctive minarets, one on each of the building’s four corners. It formed the centrepiece around which Hyderabad was planned.
   </string>
    <string name="t4"> Now regarded as one of the supreme architectural achievements of the Quṭb Shāhī period, the Charminar is a grand architectural composition in Indo-Saracenic style. It is built of granite and lime mortar with stucco ornamentation. The square structure measures 66 feet (20 metres) to a side. Each side faces one of the cardinal directions and has a pointed arch that is 36 feet (11 metres) wide at the base and reaches 66 feet high at its apex. A multisided column rises on each corner of the structure and, atop a lotus-leaf base, continues upward until it culminates in a minaret with a dome-shaped roof 160 feet (49 metres) above the ground. Each minaret is accessed via a spiral staircase on its interior wall and consists of four levels, each of which features a delicately colonnaded covered walkway around the exterior wall. Above the arches of the main structure are two stories. The first was once used as a madrasah (Islamic college) in the Quṭb Shāhī era, and the second houses a small mosque. In addition to the mosque, the Charminar has 45 other prayer areas. The Charminar’s roof and minarets afford panoramic views of Hyderabad, notably the historic Golconda Fort to the west and the bustling Lad Bazaar—adjacent to the Charminar—which is famed for its traditional lacquer bangles studded with coloured glass and stones.</string>
    <string name="t5">CLICK the button to show Directions
    </string>
    <string name="t6">Near By Places you Must Visit</string>
    <string name="t7">CLICK the button to show Directions</string>
    <string name="t9">MACCA MASJID</string>
    <string name="t10">Makkah Masjid or Mecca Masjid, is a congregational mosque in Hyderabad, India. It is one of the largest mosques in India with a capacity of 10,000 people. The mosque was built during the 17th century, and is a state-protected monument.</string>
    <string name="t11">Click Here to get the Directions </string>
    <string name="t12">PURANI HAVELI</string>
    <string name="t14">Purani Haveli one of the popular tourist spots in Hyderabad was later acquired by Asaf Jah II, the second Nizam of Hyderabad in 18th century who renovated the palace and designated the same to his son Sikandar Jah, the third Nizam of Hyderabad. Later Shikandar Jah moved to the Khilaurat complex. From then on, the place has been popularly known as Purani Haveli, which literally means ‘Old Palace’. In 19th century, the sixth Nizam of Hyderabad Nawab Mir Mahboob Ali Khan Siddiqi again made this place as his official residence. It was then the glory and grandeur of past was returned to Purani Haveli.</string>
    <string name="t15">Here are some best hotels for you</string>
    <string name="t16">HOTEL CHARMINAR</string>
    <string name="textview">FabHotel Mansingh Begum Bazar Road</string>
    <string name="t18">Guides available near Charminar</string>
    <string name="it">Hyderabad City Tourist Guide</string>
    <string name="gt">GOLCONDA FORT</string>
    <string name="gt1">HISTORY-</string>
    <string name="gt2">Founded in the approximately 12th Century by the Kakatiya Kings, this massive Golconda Fort with eight gates and 87 bastions was later built by Qutub Shahi Kings.

The name Golconda Fort has a legend behind it. As per the story, a shepherd boy was once walking on this hill when he had come across a God idol. The news about the shepherd boy and his findings reached the then ruler of Kakatiya Dynasty. The King then decided to built a fort on the hill, which then came to be known as Golconda (Shepherd’s Hill) Fort.

However, almost 200 years later, the fort came under Bahamani rulers. Later Qutub Shahi Kings took the fort under their control and extended it further. The fort was fortified and expanded during the reign of Bahamani rulers and Qutub Shahi Dynasty. Later in 1687, this fort came under the rule of Mughal emperor Aurangzeb. It was then the fort was left unattended.

At present, the Golconda Fort constitutes a complex layout of palaces, mosques and pavilion, all of which unfortunately are in ruins now.

It is said that Golconda used to be a famous diamond market attracting merchants from all over the world. It was at Golconda that the famous Kohinoor and Hope diamonds along with others such as The Regent Diamond, Darya-e Nur, Nur-Ul-Ain Diamond were stored.
</string>
    <string name="gt3">
ARCHITECTURE-</string>
    <string name="gt4">With perimeters of around 11 kilometers, the fort has 15 to 18 foot high walls. It has huge gates that have pointed iron spikes on them. This protected the fort from Elephants damaging the fort as well as enemy attacks. Golconda fort presents a mesmerizing architecture which will astonish you at each and every step. This fort has been built on a granite rock with a height of 12 meters. Huge rampart around the golconda fort was built, a glimpse of which can still be seen.

The system of acoustics in the Fort is something which attracts each and every visitor. The sound of clapping at the entrance can be heard at the Bala Hissar which is the highest point and almost a kilometre away. This system was apparently used for communication purposes, especially to alert royal in case of any attack.

Other attractive features of the Fort include water supply system which does leave many marvelling at the advancement of the technical and scientific knowledge while constructing this fort. Another popular aspect is the Rahban cannon.

Ramdas’ prison is one of the popular spots inside the fort. According to legend, Ramdas who was a revenue collector in Abdul Hasan Shahs court was imprisoned. During his imprisonment, he carved Hindu deities on the wall of his cell. One can see many carvings of Hindu Lord Hanuman on the wall, which are now smeared with holy vermillion. A holy lamp or two (diyas) is also kept lit in front of the carvings.

The main entrance of the fort is named Fatesh Darwaza, which means Victory Gate in english. It was named after Aurangzeb’s army had entered the fort through this gate. Not just for the victory procession of his army, this gate is also attracts visitors with its marvelous acoustics.

Showcasing an architectural excellence, this gate has been built in such a way that if one claps at a certain point of the entrance, then the sound of clapping can be heard at the top most pavillion. Another attractive feature of Golconda Fort is the 80 feet tree which is said to be more than 800 years old.

The fort also consists of many mounted cannons and drawbridges. Huge halls, mosques, eight gateways, and stables add on to the immense enormity of its magnificent architecture. There is speculation that a secretive tunnel starts from Durbar hall and ends at the foot of the hill. It is believed to be a secret passage to escape in case of any attack. However, no such passage has been found till date.
</string>
    <string name="gt5">CLick here to Get Directions</string>
    <string name="gt6">Near by places you must visit</string>
    <string name="gt8">NTR is considered as one of the expensive gardens of India which is spread in an area of around 55 acres. The garden has the memorial of Late NT Rama Rao. The garden is situated near Hussain Sagar lake. It has shrubs, trees, flowers, and various other types of plants which increases its attractiveness.</string>
    <string name="gt9">Chowmahalla Palace
</string>
    <string name="gt10">Chowmahalla palace was the seat of Asif Jahi dynasty and was the residence of Nizams of Hyderabad. The construction of the palace was started by Salabat Khan in 1750 and was completed by Afzalad Dawlah in between 1857 and 1869. There are two courtyards in the palace. Along with this, the palace also has darbar hall, fountains, and gardens.

</string>
    <string name="gt11">Near by Hotels and Restaurants</string>
    <string name="gt12">Green Bawarchi Restaurant</string>
    <string name="bt">Birla Mandir is a Hindu temple, built on a 280 feet (85 m) high hillock called Naubath Pahad on a 13 acres (53,000 m2) plot in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. The construction took 10 years and was opened in 1976 by Swami Ranganathananda of Ramakrishna Mission. The temple was constructed by Birla Foundation, which has also constructed several similar temples across India, all of which are known as Birla Mandir.
        Apart from the main shrine, the consorts of Lord Venkateswara, Padmavati and Andal are housed in separate shrines. The temple also has separate shrines for various Deva and Devi including Shiva, Shakti, Ganesh, Hanuman, Brahma, Saraswati and Lakshmi. Selected because teachings of men and Gurbani are engraved on temple walls. Birla temples are open to all, as identified by Mahatma Gandhi and other Hindu leaders</string>
    <string name="bt1">The temple manifests a blend of Dravidian, Rajasthani and Utkala architectures. It is constructed of 2000 tons of pure white marble. The granite idol of presiding deity Venkateswara is about 11 ft (3.4 m) tall and a carved lotus forms an umbrella on the top. There is a brass flagstaff in the temple premises which rises to a height of 42 ft (13 m). The temple does not have traditional bells, as Swami Ranganathananda wished that the temple atmosphere should be conducive for meditation.</string>
    <string name="bt3">Hyderabad is a branch center of Ramakrishna Math  Ramakrishna Mission, Belur, Howrah, West Bengal.

We are a worldwide, non-political, non-sectarian spiritual organizations which have been engaged in various forms of humanitarian, social service activities for more than a century. Inspired by the ideals of renunciation and service, the monks and lay devotees of the Math and Mission serve millions of men, women and children, without any distinction of caste, religion or race, because they see the living God in them.

The organizations were brought into existence by Sri Ramakrishna (1836-1886), the great 19th century saint from Bengal who is regarded as the Prophet of the Modern Age, and Sri Ramakrishna’s chief disciple, Swami Vivekananda (1863-1902), one of the foremost thinkers and religious leaders of the present age, who is regarded as ‘one of the main moulders of the modern world, in the words of an eminent Western scholar A.L. Basham.</string>
    <string name="idly">Firstly, in a large mixing bowl soak 2 cup idli rice for 5 hours. alternatively, use dosa rice / sona masuri rice. in another bowl soak 1 cup urad dal for 3 hours. drain off the water from urad dal and blend to smooth paste adding water as required. transfer the smooth and fluffy batter of urad dal into a large bowl. in the blender take soaked rice and add ¾ cup of washed thin poha. bend to slightly coarse paste adding water as required. transfer the rice batter to the bowl of urad dal batter. mix well making sure everything is combined well. now cover and rest in warm place for 8-10 hours or till the batter ferments and doubles. after 8 hours, batter doubles indicating well fermented with air pockets present. add 1½ tsp salt to the batter and mix well. mix gently without disturbing the air pockets. now grease the thatte idli plate with oil. scoop the batter into idli plate greased with oil. arrange the idli plate into the stand. steam for 20 minutes on medium flame or till a tooth pick inserted comes out clean. finally, thatte idlis are ready to serve along with chutney and sambar.</string>
    <string name="nee"><br>Firstly, in a large mixing bowl soak 2 cup idli rice for 5 hours. alternatively, use dosa rice / sona masuri rice.</br>\n
<br>1.in another bowl soak 1 cup urad dal for 3 hours.</br>\n
<br>2.drain off the water from urad dal and blend to smooth paste adding water as required.</br> \n
<br>3.transfer the smooth and fluffy batter of urad dal into a large bowl.</br> \n
<br>4.in the blender take soaked rice and add ¾ cup of washed thin poha.</br> \n
<br>5.bend to slightly coarse paste adding water as required.</br> \n
<br>6.transfer the rice batter to the bowl of urad dal batter.</br> \n
<br>7.mix well making sure everything is combined well.</br> \n
<br>8.now cover and rest in warm place for 8-10 hours or till the batter ferments and doubles.</br> \n
<br>9.after 8 hours, batter doubles indicating well fermented with air pockets present.</br> \n
<br>10.add 1½ tsp salt to the batter and mix well.</br> \n
<br>11.mix gently without disturbing the air pockets.</br> \n
<br>12.now grease the thatte idli plate with oil.</br> \n
<br>13.scoop the batter into idli plate greased with oil.</br> \n
<br>14.arrange the idli plate into the stand.</br> \n
<br>15.steam for 20 minutes on medium flame or till a tooth pick inserted comes out clean.</br> \n
<br>16.finally, thatte idlis are ready to serve along with chutney and sambar.</br> \n</string>
    <string name="ep">1.Electric Mixer\n
2.Oven\n
3.Idly cooker\n
4.Bowls\n</string>
    <string name="nu">1.Calories: 326kcal\n
2.Carbohydrates: 66g\n
3.Protein: 12g\n
4.Fat: 1g\n
5.Saturated Fat: 1g\n
6.Polyunsaturated Fat: 1g\n
7.Monounsaturated Fat: 1g\n
8.Sodium: 780mg\n
9.Potassium: 71mg\n
10.Fiber: 7g\n
11.Sugar: 1g\n
12.Vitamin A: 2IU\n
13.Vitamin C: 1mg\n
14.Calcium: 38mg\n
15.Iron: 3mgv</string>
    <string name="di">
        1.	3 cup sona masuri rice\n
2.	½ tsp methi / fenugreek seeds\n
3.	water (for soaking)\n
4.	1 cup urad dal\n
5.	2 tbsp toor dal\n
6.	2 tbsp chana dal\n
7.	1 cup poha / avalakki (rinsed)\n

    </string>
    <string name="du">1.firstly, in a large bowl take 3 cup sona masuri rice and ½ tsp methi. \n
2.	rinse well and soak in enough water for 4 hours.\n
3.	in another bowl take 1 cup urad dal, 2 tbsp toor dal and 2 tbsp chana dal.\n
4.	rinse well and soak in enough water for 2 hours.\n
5.	after soaking dal for 2 hours, drain off the water and transfer to the grinder. you can also grind in mixi if you do not have access to a grinder.\n
6.	add water as required and blend to smooth paste.\n
7.	scrape sides. the smooth and fluffy batter will be ready after 40 minutes.\n
8.	transfer the batter to a large vessel and keep aside.\n
9.	in the same grinder add soaked rice and 1 cup rinsed poha.\n
10.	add water slowly and scrape the sides. blend to a coarse paste.\n
11.	transfer the rice batter to the same urad dal batter.\n
12.	mix well making sure everything is well combined.\n
13.	ferment in a warm place for at least 8 hours or until the batter doubles in volume. if you are living in a cold climate, then you can place the batter in the warm oven (just heat the oven until it turns slightly warm and then turn off) to ferment.\n
14.	once the batter is well fermented, mix gently, without disturbing the air pockets.\n
15.	transfer 4 cups of fermented batter to a small bowl and add 1 tsp salt.\n
16.	mix well until the salt is well combined. masala dosa batter is ready. keep aside.\n
</string>
    <string name="epp">1.Dosa pan\n
2.Electric mixer\n</string>
    <string name="njr">1.	Calories: 40kcal\n
2.	Carbohydrates: 6g\n
3.	Protein: 2g\n
4.	Fat: 1g\n
5.	Saturated Fat: 1g\n
6.	Sodium: 81mg\n
7.	Potassium: 20mg\n
8.	Fiber: 2g\n
9.	Sugar: 1g\n
10.	Vitamin A: 36IU\n
11.	Vitamin C: 6mg\n
12.	Calcium: 9mgI\n
13.	ron: 1mg \n
</string>
    <string name="om">1. 6 Eggs\n
2. 1 Tablespoon(14 grams)of sliced scallions\n
3. kosher salt and cracked black pepper\n
4. 1 Teaspoon(14 grams) of butter\n
5.Sliced scallions(to garnish)\n
6.Greek yogurt(to garnish)\n
</string>
    <string name="pi">1. Beat eggs and scallions in large bowl.Gently fold potato chips into eggs, trying to break as few as possible.
  Season with salt.\n
2. Heat pan over medium high heat add butter when foam subsides add
  eggs/chips mixture and turn heat to medium low.Using a rubber spatula gently pull
  eggs away from slides of Pan while the eggs set.\n
3. When eggs have began to set,use a oven mitt and a plate to flip over torta.Please plate over pan, and
  securing the pan to the plate with an over so torta lands on the plate,then gently slip torta back into pan to finish cooking.\n
4.Slice into segments and serve with more sliced scallions,cracked black pepper,and greek yogurt.\n
</string>
    <string name="epe">1. Bowl 1lit\n
2. Alu Slicer\n
3. Mixture\n
</string>
    <string name="pn">1. Calories: 160cl\n
2. Fat:10g\n
3. Carbohydrate:15g\n
4. Protien:2g\n
5. Fiber:1.5g\n
6. Megnesium,vitamin C andB6\n</string>
    <string name="ri">
1. wheat flour 2 cups\n

2. methi leaves/fenugreek leaves (chopped leaves alone) 2 bunches\n

3. salt (powdered) 1 teaspoon\n

4. turmeric powder 1/2 teaspoon\n

5. oil (for the dough) 2 tablespoons\n

6. dhania powder 1 teaspoon\n

7. red chilly powder 1 teaspoon\n

8. ajwain/thymol seeds 1/2 teaspoon\n
</string>
    <string name="rv">1.Mix all the ingredients in a mixing bowl\n

2.Sprinkle enough water and knead to a smooth dough\n

3.Make chapatis of medium thickness\n

4.Roast on a hot tawa using half a Teaspoon of oil for both sides of each chapati\n


</string>
    <string name="bm"> 1.Modern Foods 100% Whole Wheat Brown Bread – 2 Slices\n
2.	Eggs – 1 Large or 2 Small\n
3.	Oil – 1.5 tsp (you may also use a single square of butter)\n
4.	Green Chilli – 1, finely chopped\n
5.	Onion, finely chopped – 1 tbsp\n
6.	Capsicum, finely chopped – 1 tbsp\n
7.	Salt – as per taste\n
8.	Pepper – as per taste\n
9.	Chaat masala – as per taste\n
10.	Sandwich spread or Ketchup\n
11.	Grated cheese or cheese slice\n</string>
    <string name="sbff">1.	Whisk the egg in a bowl till the mix turns frothy.\n
2.	Add the veggies, green chillies, followed by the desired seasoning, and mix well..\n
3.	Add your oil to a flat cooking pan, and let it heat..\n
4.	Drop the egg mixture onto the heated pan, spread it uniformly and let it cook for 2 minutes on medium flame. Flip the omelette once the sides start browning and the surface looks half cooked. Lift the omelette up from the flat pan..\n
5.	Place one slice of bread on the same pan to toast it. Meanwhile, place the omelette on top of the bread and fold it in a square shape. You may alternatively first place the cheese slice/grated cheese in the middle before folding it in. Allow the cheese to melt..\n
6.	Place the other bread slice on top and then flip it so that the other bread slice gets toasted..\n
7.	Once the surface crisps up, take it off heat..\n
8.	Slice the sandwich into half and serve warm..\n</string>
    <string name="jgj">1.  1 Kg Meat\n
2.  1 tbsp Salt\n
3.  1 tbsp Ginger-garlic paste\n
4.  1 tbsp Red chilli paste1 tbsp Green chilli paste (sauteed brown onions to taste)\n
5.  1/2 tbsp Cardamom powder\n
6.  3-4 Cinnamon sticks\n
7.  1 tbsp Cumin seeds\n
8.  4 Cloves\n
9.  A pinch of Mace\n
10. To taste Mint leaves\n
11. 2 tbsp Lemon juice\n
11. 250\ gms Curd\n
12. 4 tbsp Clarified butter\n
13. 750 gms Semi-cooked rice\n
14. 1 tsp Saffron strand\n
15. 1/2 cup Water\n
16. 1/2 cup Oil\n
17. Boiled eggs\n
18. sliced Carrots\n
19. Cucumbers\n
</string>
    <string name="bii">1.Clean the meat. Now in a pan, add meat, salt, ginger garlic paste, red chilli   powder, green chilli paste, sauteed brown onions, cardamom powder, cinnamon, cumin seeds, cloves, mace, mint leaves and lemon juice.\n
2.Mix all of these ingredients thoroughly together.\n
3.Add curd, clarified butter, semi-cooked rice, saffron, water and oil. Mix it well.\n
4.Now apply sticky dough on the sides of the pan.\n
5.Cover it with a lid and cook for about 25 minutes.\n
6.Hyderabadi biryani is ready to eat.\n
7.Garnish it with boiled eggs, sliced carrots, cucumbers and serve hot\n
</string>
    <string name="bee">
1. Pan\n
2. Bowl\n
3. Pressure cooker\n
4. Mixer grinder\n
</string>
    <string name="pii">
1. 12 cashew nuts\n
2. 2 tomatoes chopped\n
3. 1 green chilli chopped\n
4. 1/4 inch of ginger\n
5. 3 Tbsp oil\n
6. 1 tsp cumin seeds\n
7. 1 bay leaf\n
8. 1 tsp coriander powder\n
9. 1/4 tsp turmeric \n
10. 1/4 tsp red chilli powder,adujst to taste\n
11. 1 tsp sugar\n
12. 1 tsp salt, adjust to taste\n
13. 1/4 tsp garam masala\n
14. Butter as you want\n
</string>
    <string name="piii">1. Slice paneer into 3/4 inch cubes. Keep aside.\n
2. Grind cashews into powder-like consistency. Keep aside.\n
3. Puree tomatoes, green chili and ginger. Keep aside.\n
4. Add oil in a pan, over medium heat. Shallow fry paneer cubes till they turn slightly brown.\n
   Remove from pan and place over paper towels to absorb excess oil.\n
5. Increase heat to medium-high and test the oil by adding one cumin seed. If it cracks
   immediately, the oil is ready.\n
6. Add cumin seeds to the oil and as they crack, add asafoetida and bay leaves. Stir for a
   few seconds.\n
7. Add tomato puree, coriander powder, turmeric, red chili powder, and paprika. Cook the
   mixture, stirring occasionally for 2-3 minutes. It will reduce to half its volume and start
   separating from the oil.\n
8. Add sugar, cashew powder and yogurt. Cook for another minute then add 1 cup of water
   and salt and bring to boil.\n
9. Add paneer and cover the pan. Simmer for a few minutes over medium-low heat, till gravy
   is slightly thick in consistency.\n
10. Remove from heat, add garam masala and chopped cilantro. Mix gently, cover the pan
    and let it sit for a couple of minutes.\n
11. Shahi paneer tastes best if it is served hot.\n
</string>
    <string name="pe">1.Bowl\n
2.mixture\n
3.kithen instruments\n
</string>
    <string name="ck">
1.  4 fairly small boneless, skinless chicken breasts (about 600g)\n
2.  25g low-fat natural yoghurt\n
3.  1 tbsp sunﬂower oil\n
2   large onions, chopped (400g prepared weight)\n
4   garlic cloves, peeled and sliced\n
5.  20g chunk of fresh root ginger, peeled and ﬁnely grated\n
6.  12 cardamom pods, seeds crushed\n
7.  1 tbsp ground cumin\n
8.  1 tbsp ground coriander\n
9.  ½ heaped tsp ground turmeric\n
10. ¼ tsp hot chilli powder\n
11. 1 bay leaf\n
12. 4 whole cloves\n
13. 1 tbsp plain ﬂour\n
14. small pinch of saﬀron\n
15. 2 tsp caster sugar\n
16. ½ tsp ﬁne sea salt, plus extra to season\n
17. 300ml cold water\n
18. 3 tbsp double cream\n
19. freshly ground black pepper\n
20. fresh coriander, roughly torn, to garnish (optional)\n
</string>
    <string name="cki">1.Cut each chicken breast into 8 or 9 bite-sized pieces,season with black pepper and put them in a non-metallic bowl. Stir in the yoghurt, cover with cling ﬁlm and chill for a minimum of 30 minutes but ideally 2–6 hours.\n
2.Heat the oil in a large, non-stick saucepan and add the onions, garlic and ginger. Cover and cook over a low heat for 15 minutes until very soft and lightly coloured. Stir the onions occasionally so they don’t start to stick\n
3.Once the onions are softened, stir in the crushed cardamom seeds, cumin, coriander, turmeric, chilli powder and bay leaf. Pinch oﬀ the ends of the cloves into the pan and throw away the stalks. Cook the spices with the onions for 5 minutes, stirring constantly.\n
4.Stir in the ﬂour, saﬀron, sugar and ½ a teaspoon of salt, then slowly pour the water into the pan, stirring constantly. Bring to a gentle simmer, then cover and cook for 10 minutes, stirring occasionally. Remove the pan from the heat, take out the bay leaf and blitz the onion mixture with a stick blender until it is as smooth as possible. You can do this in a food processor if you prefer, but let the mixture cool slightly ﬁrst. The sauce can now be used right away or cooled, covered and chilled until 10 minutes before serving.\n
5.Drain the chicken in a colander over the sink, shaking it a few times – you want the meat to have just a light coating of yoghurt. Place a non-stick frying pan on the heat, add the sauce and bring it to a simmer. Add the chicken pieces and cream and cook for about 10 minutes or until the chicken is tender and cooked through, stirring regularly. Exactly how long the chicken takes will depend on the size of your pieces, so check a piece after 8 minutes – there should be no pink remaining.\n
6.Adjust the seasoning to taste, spoon into a warmed serving dish and serve garnished with fresh coriander if you like.

</string>
    <string name="ti">1.Arge firm tomatoes – sliced thinly\n
2.Kosher salt\n
3.Cooking spray\n
4.Edible vegtable Oil\n
5.Sugar 3spoons\n
6.Pepper power\n
7.Garlic\n
8.Tomato power\n
9.Wheat fibre\n

</string>
    <string name="tii">1. Lay sliced tomatoes on a cutting board.\n
2. Sprinkle generously with salt, let sit for 15 minutes.\n
3. Pat the tomatoes with a paper towel to soak up the moisture.\n
4. Flip the tomatoes and repeat steps 1, 2, and 3.\n
5. Grease a flat, microwaveable plate with cooking spray.\n
6. Arrange seasoned tomato slices on the plate and spray some cooking oil.\n
7. Microwave for a minute, flip the tomatoes over, and microwave for another minute.\n
8.Transfer the tomato chips to a cooling rack and enjoy!\n

</string>
    <string name="te">1.Copper bowl\n
2.Slicer\n
3.knief\n
4. mixture\n
</string>
    <string name="po">
1.Add the crispy puffed rice to a large mixing bowl, followed by masala chana dal, roasted peanuts,
  crushed papdi, chopped onion, tomato, potato, spices - salt, chaat masala,
  and red chili powder (or green chili finely chopped), raw mango pieces, and cilantro.\n

2.Add the three chutneys - red garlic chutney, spicy green chutney, and sweet tamarind chutney
   along with lemon juice. Start with a little, and then add more as required to your taste.\n

3 and 4 - Finally, add the sev and mix until evenly coated.\n
 Bhel is ready!! Serve as is or garnished with more sev, masala chana dal,
 raw mango, pomegranate pearls, and cilantro.\n
</string>
    <string name="bu">1. 3 cups puffed rice murmura, mamra\n
2. 2 tablespoon masala chana dal\n
3. 2 tablespoon roasted peanuts\n
4. 5-6 papdi crushed, plus more for serving (optional)\n
5. ¼ cup red onion finely chopped\n
6. ¼ cup tomato finely chopped\n
7. ½ cup potato boiled, peeled and chopped\n
8. ¼ teaspoon salt optional, adjust to taste\n
9. ¼ teaspoon chaat masala\n
10. ¼ teaspoon chilli powder\n
11. 1-2 tablespoon raw mango finely chopped\n
12. 2 tablespoon cilantro leaves finely chopped\n
13. 1 tablespoon red garlic chutney\n
14. 1-2 tablespoon green chutney adjust to taste\n
15. 4-5 tablespoon date-tamarind chutney\n
</string>
</resources>